Guide to the German Correspondence from the World Wars Collection 1916-1946 MSS 161 MSS.161
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Gottlob Zieher
  With the exception of a single letter, dated February 18, 1943, Gottlob Zieher's correspondence is comprised of letters received. The majority of these are letters from Zieher's siblings, many from Frieda Zieher, who wrote from the family's hometown, Dinkelsbühl. The last letter sent to Zieher, from his sister Lina, is dated August 20, 1944.
  - Brand, Ernst- April 5, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 388)
  - Doberer, Wilhelm- September 24, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Fischer, Luise- July 25, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 390)
  - Fischer, Luise- June 19, 1944- July 23, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Jung, Willy- January 13, 1942- March 3, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 392)
  - [ ], Marie- May 10, 1941- June 1, 1944, 1941-1944 (Box 16, Folder 393)
  - Zieher, Ernst- April 5, 1938- January 9, 1940, 1938-1940 (Box 16, Folder 394)
  - Zieher, Ernst- January 13, 1940- July 12, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 395)
  - Zieher, Ernst- May 25, 1941- June 2, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 396)
  - Zieher, Ernst- June 16, 1942- March 5, 1943, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 397)
  - Zieher, Ernst- October 11, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 398)
  - Zieher, Frieda- May 8, 1941- November 10, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 399)
  - Zieher, Frieda- November 5, 1941- February 1, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 400)
  - Zieher, Frieda- February 7, 1942- May 29, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 401)
  - Zieher, Frieda- June 7, 1942- December 10, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 402)
  - Zieher, Frieda- December 12, 1942- May 3, 1943, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Zieher, Frieda- May 9, 1943- October 4, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Zieher, Frieda- October 9, 1943- March 1, 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 405)
  - Zieher, Frieda- March 5, 1944- June 18, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 406)
  - Zieher, Frieda- July 2, 1944- July 27, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 407)
  - Zieher, Fritz- May 27, 1941- July 2, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 408)
  - Zieher, Fritz- June 15, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 409)
  - Zieher, Fritz- undated (Box 16, Folder 409a)
  - Zieher, Gottlob- February 18, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 410)
  - Zieher, Karl- May 17, 1941- October 30, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Zieher, Karl- February 9, 1943- July 20, 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 412)
  - Zieher, Lina- June 8, 1941- February 14, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 413)
  - Zieher, Lina- May 26, 1943- August 20, 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 414)
  - Zieher, Maria- November 10, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 415)
  - [ ], Kurt- March 8, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 416)
  - [ ], Hans- August 24, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 417)
  - Unidentified- November 19, 1941- March 16, 1944, 1941-1944 (Box 16, Folder 418)
- Series X: Miscellaneous wartime documents
  Series X contains miscellaneous items that, at the time of acquisition, were, seemingly arbitrarily, grouped with the correspondence of Gottlob Zieher. These items, labelled as miscellaneous documents, include soldier identification books, certificates of military honor, and an application to the Evangelical church, among others.
  - Miscellaneous documents- 1935-1945 (Box 16, Folder 419)
- Oversize: Series VI- Pietro Schiavi and Shirley Messinger
  All three items placed in oversize are from Series VI: Schiavi and Messinger.
  - Letter from Pietro Schiavi with colored newspaper clippings- October 22, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 217a)
  - "Gioia: Settimanale Femminile" (Italian women's magazine)- March 7, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 219a)
  - Newspaper clipping: "Their Teachers and Classmates Hail Them as State's Outstanding Girl Citizens"- March 11, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 222a)